Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Subject Files
2.1.3.6
Marist College
  Box 1537 - Box 1540
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1541
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Colorado Springs, circa 1970s; 1 (Box 1541)
    - In Colorado Springs after a hospital session in Denver, 1
    - Verso: In Colorado Springs after a hospital session in Denver, 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a woman and a horse in Colorado Springs], 2
  - Subject files: Coronado Hotel, San Diego, circa 1950; 2 (Box 1541)
    - Lt. Gen. [Lieutenant General] Leo D. Hermle, USMC (ret.) (in tuxedo) [Lowell Thomas on crutches], 1
    - Verso: Lt. Gen. [Lieutenant General] Leo D. Hermle, USMC (ret.) (in tuxedo) [Lowell Thomas on crutches], 1-verso
    - [left to right: Lowell Thomas, Jr., unidentified man, Lowell Thomas (on crutches)], 2
    - LT and 4 Admirals; When LT entertained the largest number of Admirals ever gathered in history of the world; at Coronado, San Diego, 3
    - Verso: LT and 4 Admirals; When LT entertained the largest number of Admirals ever gathered in history of the world; at Coronado, San Diego, 3-verso
    - When LT entertained the largest number of Admirals ever gathered in history of the world; at Coronado, San Diego, 4
    - When LT entertained the largest number of Admirals ever gathered in history of the world; at Coronado, San Diego, 5
  - Subject files: Herford Tynes Cowling (photographs of Africa and Asia), circa 1920s; 3 (Box 1541)
    - A celebration of Cowling"s native bearer's at night, after the first lion was killed. This was taken by burning actinic flares, which at first frightened the natives, 1
    - Verso: A celebration of Cowling"s native bearer's at night, after the first lion was killed. This was taken by burning actinic flares, which at first frightened the natives, 1-verso
    - Kanawana[?] Women, Kenya, 2
    - Verso: Kanawana[?] Women, Kenya, 2-verso
    - [Two native women of Kenya], 3
    - [Native women of Kenya with a horn], 4
    - [Group of native Kenya women], 5
    - [Kenyan man with elaborate head dress], 6
    - [Line of people carrying gear in Kenya], 7
    - [People riding elephants through tall grass in Kenya], 8
    - [Tribe of natives in Kenya], 9
    - [Three native African men wearing fake beards], 10
    - [Three men riding an elephant in Africa], 11
    - [Statues of faces made in stone in Africa (?)], 12
    - [Lake and stone structures in Africa (?)], 13
    - [Group of Africans standing in front of equipment], 14
    - [Line of natives in Africa carrying gear], 15
    - [Camp set up in Africa], 16
    - [Two men filming in Africa], 17
    - [Two men filming with a camouflaged camera in Africa], 18
    - [Man in Africawith a gun], 19
    - [Tiger skins on a fence in Africa], 20
    - [People standing beneath a dragon statue in Asia], 21
    - [People riding on elephants in Asia (?)], 22
    - [Man touching wooden barrel in Asia], 23
    - [Man with pipe filming in Asia], 24
    - [Man's campsite at a mountain base in Asia], 25
    - [Man standing with two peope in traditional Asian costumes], 26
    - [Man filming in front of a small mountain range], 27
    - [Man in traditional Asian clothing with an Asian man], 28
    - [Asian woman with elaborate headpiece], 29
    - [Asian women dancing in traditional garb], 30
    - [Two Asian wimen performing in traditional Asian costumes], 31
  - Subject files: Violet Olivia Cressy-Marcks, circa 1930; 4 (Box 1541)
    - [Portrait of Violet Olivia Cressy-Marcks], 1
  - Subject files: Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (Doctor Haskell Cohen), circa 1950s; 5 (Box 1541)
    - Dr. Haskell Cohen; 87 years old - one time associate of LT, Sr.'s father, Victor-Cripple Creek, 1
    - Verso: Dr. Haskell Cohen; 87 years old - one time associate of LT, Sr.'s father, Victor-Cripple Creek, 1-verso
  - Subject files: Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado [cabinet cards], undated; 6 (Box 1541)
    - [Run down building at Cripple Creek, Colorado], 1
    - [Destroyed building at Cripple Creek], 2
    - [Town in Colorado], 3
    - [Some type of factory in Colorado], 4
    - [Storefront street in Colorado], 5
    - [Barren hill with smoke in the background in Colorado], 6
    - [Group of men underground (?) in Colorado], 7
    - [Busy town street], 8
    - [Town in Colorado], 9
    - [Caption: Islabella Mine Northslope Hill], 10
    - [Group of people on a picnic in Colorado (?)], 11
    - [Group of people in Colorado (?)], 12
    - [Group of people on a log bridge in Colorado (?)], 13
  - Subject files: Homer Croy, undated; 7 (Box 1541)
    - Homer Croy is the only cowboy in the state of Arizona who has his name on his license plate, 1
    - Verso: Homer Croy is the only cowboy in the state of Arizona who has his name on his license plate, 1-verso
  - Subject files: Curtiss-Wright Corporation, 1943 October 20-29; 8 (Box 1541)
    - Wright Aircraft - Buffalo, Gene Sarazen and B[?] Wright; Photograph from files of Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, Buffalo, N.Y., 1
    - Verso: Wright Aircraft - Buffalo, Gene Sarazen and B[?] Wright; Photograph from files of Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, Buffalo, N.Y., 1-verso
    - Gene Sarazen; Photograph from files of Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, Buffalo, N.Y., 2
    - Verso: Gene Sarazen; Photograph from files of Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, Buffalo, N.Y., 2-verso
    - Verso: Oct 29, 1943, 3
    - Verso: Oct 29, 1943, 3-verso
    - L.T. at Child Care Center of Curtiss Wright plant in Buffalo, 4
    - Verso: L.T. at Child Care Center of Curtiss Wright plant in Buffalo; Photograph from files of Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, Buffalo, N.Y., 4-verso
    - L.T. at Child Care Center of Curtiss Wright plant in Buffalo, 5
    - [Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas at Child Care Center of Curtiss-Wright plant], 6
    - Gene Sarazen, right; Note: Construction of the Curtiss P-40 Warhawk fuselage being explained by Mr. E. F. Drollinger for Mr. Gene Sarazen, Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas; Curtis-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, New York State Plants, 20 October, 1943, 7
    - Verso: Gene Sarazen, right; Photograph from files of Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, Buffalo, N.Y., 7-verso
    - Note: Construction of the Curtiss P-40 Warhawk fuselage being explained by Mr. E. F. Drollinger for Mr. Gene Sarazen, Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas; Curtis-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, New York State Plants, 20 October, 1943, 8
    - Photograph from files of Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, Buffalo, N.Y, 9
  - Subject files: Dartmouth panel, 1977 July; 9 (Box 1541)
    - Note: [stenographic note and letter from Lowell Thomas to Ray Kroc], 1
    - [Dartmouth panel], 2
    - [Dartmouth panel], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas about to speak at Dartmouth], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a school official at Dartmouth], 5
  - Subject files: Mary Davis, circa 1920s - 1930s; 10 (Box 1541)
    - [Lowell Thomas at dinner with Mary Davis and others], 1
    - [Portrait of Mary Davis], 2
    - [Portrait of Mary Davis], 3
    - [Portrait of Mary Davis], 4
    - [Profile of Mary Davis], 5
    - [Portrait of Mary Davis], 6
    - [Photograph of Mary Davis and another woman], 7
  - Subject files: Armand Denis, circa 1960s; 11 (Box 1541)
    - [Unidentified man and woman laying in the sand], 1
    - Note that came with 11.1 concerning Armand Denis, 2
  - Subject files: Denver, circa 1950s - 1960s; 12 (Box 1541)
    - Danny Sullivan [from Cripple Creek, Colorado] - who saved TR [Teddy Roosevelt], 1
    - Verso: Danny Sullivan [from Cripple Creek, Colorado] - who saved TR [Teddy Roosevelt], 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and four other men in Denver], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas with a group of men in Denver], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with a man in Denver], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas at a table with a man and women in Denver], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with a man and woman at a table in Denver], 6
    - [A banquet for an event in Denver], 7
    - [Portrait of an unidentified man], 8
    - [Smiling elderly woman], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas and three men sitting around a model for a building], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas and two men presenting a building model], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas and three men holding a building model], 12
  - Subject files: Der Ling, circa 1920s; 13 (Box 1541)
    - Caption: To Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas, Most sincerely yours, Der Ling, 1
  - Subject files: Detroit, circa 1940s; 14 (Box 1541)
    - [Lowell Tomas and two others around a WJR radio microphone], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas being broadcasted on WJR], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and a group of men in Detroit], 3
  - Subject files: Thomas E. Dewey, circa 1940s; 15 (Box 1541)
    - [Lowell Thomas with his golfing friends], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a group of men], 2
  - Subject files: Dionne quintuplets, 1941; 16 (Box 1541)
    - Caption: Emilie, Cecile, Yvonne, Marie, Annette, 1
    - Note: THE QUINTUPLETS GET A NEW NURSE: the Dionne Quintuplets were eager to show off their ability with camera, drawing pencil, musical instruments, etc., for their new nurse, Mlle. Gertrude Provencher, of the city of Quebec. L. to r.: Emilie, Yvonne (on floor, drawing), Cecile, Nurse Gertrude Provencher, Marie (with finger in mouth, tsk! tsk!), and Annette, 2
    - Caption: Annette, Emilie, Yvonne, Marie, Cecile, 3
    - Note: CECILE INCHING AHEAD IN QUINTUPLET GROWTH RACE: The Dionne Quints line up to be weighed, always a thrilling moment, for each is eager to grow faster than her sisters. Left to right: Annette, Emilie, Yvonne, Marie and Cecile, with Nurse Doreen Chaput, 4
  - Subject files: Disney World [Lowell Thomas's 80th birthday], 1972; 17 (Box 1541)
    - [Lowell Thomas at Disney World for his 80th birthday], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and another man in front of Cinderella's castle in Disney World], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas in Disney World], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas walking through Disney World on his 80th birthday], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and a tour guide in Disney World], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas with a group on Main Street in Disney World], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas in Disney World on his 80th birthday], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas and a tour guide walking towards Disney World], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas and a tourguide waiting on line for Disney World], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas and his group in Disney World], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas at Disney World], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas on jungle cruise ride in Disney World], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking into the microphone on the boat ride in Disney World], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas on the Jungle Cruise ride in Disney World], 14
    - [Water skiers holding flags that spell out "Thanks Lowell"], 15
  - Subject files: Disney World [Lowell Thomas's 80th birthday], 1972; 18 (Box 1541)
    - [Tay Thomas, Jr. at right], 1
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, second from right], 2
    - Gen. [General James "Jimmy" ] Doolittle, 3
    - Verso: Gen. [General James "Jimmy" ] Doolittle, 3-verso
    - [General James "Jimmy" Doolittle with Lowell Thomas], 4
    - [General James "Jimmy" Doolittle], 5
    - [General James "Jimmy" Doolittle], 6
    - Verso: Colonel [Bernt] Balchen, 7
    - Verso: Captain Eddie [Rickenbacker], 8
    - Verso: Kay Taylor, 9
    - Verso: Sue Prosser, 10
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to a man in Disney World], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas celebrating his 80th birthday in Disney World], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas and Mickey Mouse on his 80th birthday], 13
    - [Disney band and characters playing in front of the entrace to Disney World], 14
    - [Brer Bear and Brer Fox performing for Lowell Thomas on his 80th birthday], 15
  - Subject files: Disney World [Lowell Thomas's 80th birthday] [contact sheets], 1972; 19 (Box 1541)
    - [contact sheets from Lowell Thomas's 80th birthday at Disney World], 1
    - [contact sheets from Lowell Thomas's 80th birthday at Disney World], 2
    - [contact sheets from Lowell Thomas's 80th birthday at Disney World], 3
    - [contact sheets from Lowell Thomas's 80th birthday at Disney World], 4
    - [contact sheets from Lowell Thomas's 80th birthday at Disney World], 5
    - [contact sheets from Lowell Thomas's 80th birthday at Disney World], 6
  - Subject files: Disney World [Lowell Thomas's 80th birthday] [color photographs], 1972; 20 (Box 1541)
    - Note: [letter from Mrs. Robert Trent Jones to Lowell Thomas discussing photographs from Disney World], 1
    - Note: [note that was included with Disney World photos], 2
    - Note: [note that was included with Disney World photos], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr., center, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at right], 4
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas], 5
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, seated at center], 6
    - [Tay Thomas, Jr. at right], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to a woman on a boat], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas and others on a boat at Disney World], 10
    - [The boat used for Lowell Thomas's 80th birthday party], 11
    - [The boat where Lowell Thomas had his 80th birthday party], 12
    - [Boat on which Lowell Thomas celebrated his 80th birthday], 13
    - The boat where Lowell Thomas had his 80th birthday party], 14
    - [Disney's contemporary resort], 15
    - [Palm trees outside of a building in Disney World], 16
    - [Three unidentified party guests of Lowell Thomas], 17
    - [Unidentified man and woman attending Lowell Thomas's 80th birthday party at Disney World], 18
    - [Beach at the Polynesian Resort in Disney World], 19
    - [Beach at the Polynesian Resort in Disney World], 20
    - [Swimming pool at the Polynesian Resort in Disney World], 21
    - [Lowell Thomas and Mickey Mouse during Thomas's 80th birthday celebration], 22
  - Subject files: Disney World [Lowell Thomas's 80th birthday] [color photographs], 1972; 21 (Box 1541)
    - [left to right: Tay Thomas, Jr., Lowell Thomas, Jr., Lowell Thomas, Anne Thomas, Jr.], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas (seated)], 2
    - [left to right: Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Lowell Thomas, unidentified woman], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas chatting with two unidentified men at his 80th birthday party], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas at Disney World celebrating his 80th birthday party], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas on his 80th birthday], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting on the monorail going to Disney World to celebrate his 80th birthday], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas celebrating his 80th birthday in Disney World], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas and others waiting for the train in Disney World], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas and a party guest celebrating Thomas's 80th birthday in Disney World], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with a man in Disney World], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with a group of men at Disney World], 12
    - [Brer Bear character surrounded by children in Disney World], 13
    - [The Liberty Square riverboat in Disney World], 14
    - [Cinderella's castle in Magic Kingdom, Disney World], 15
  - Subject files: Dogs, circa 1940s; 22 (Box 1541)
    - [Lowell Thomas and others with huskies], 1
    - [People standing on railroad tracks with huskies], 2
    - [Unidentified man and woman playing with two huskies], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas petting huskies], 4
    - [Unidentified man and woman petting huskies], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas at a dog show (?)], 6
  - Subject files: Dogs, undated; 23 (Box 1541)
    - For Mrs. Thomas, The Prize Boy, Basque of Basquaerie, a brother of your lamented Bouncer, 1
    - Verso: For Mrs. Thomas, The Prize Boy, Basque of Basquaerie, a brother of your lamented Bouncer, 1-verso
    - Chimo!, 2
    - Verso: Chimo!, 2-verso
    - [Dog wearing a hat in a hat box], 3
  Box 1542
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Sam Donaldson and Lowell Thomas, circa 1970s; 1 (Box 1542)
    - [Sam Donaldson and Lowell Thomas], 1
  - Subject files: James H. "Jimmy" Doolittle, 1930 - 1940s; 2 (Box 1542)
    - Caption: [left to right] Eddie Rickenbacker, Gen. Doolittle, LT [1940s], 1
    - [Left to right: Eddie Rickenbacker, General Doolittle, Lowell Thomas; 1940s], 2
    - [1930][Clock presented to Lieutenant James H. Doolittle "A regular fellow and a great piolet" P.U.D. 1930], 3
    - Note: [letter from Shell Petroleum Corporation to Lowell Thomas discussing Dolittle photographs], 4
  - Subject files: James H. "Jimmy" Doolittle [includes color photographs], 1970s; 3 (Box 1542)
    - LEFT TO RIGHT: Lowell Thomas, Senator Barry Goldwater, General James Doolittle, General R. A. Knobloch, 1
    - Verso: LEFT TO RIGHT: Lowell Thomas, Senator Barry Goldwater, General James Doolittle, General R. A. Knobloch, 1-verso
    - L.T. with Gen. Jimmy Doolittle, 2
    - Verso: L.T. with Gen. Jimmy Doolittle, 2-verso
    - Doolittle on left - [General R. A. Knobloch(?) - L.T., 3
    - Verso: Doolittle on left - [General R. A. Knobloch(?)]- L.T., 3-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with General R.A. Knobloch], 4
  - Subject files: Douglas Aircraft Company, 1952; 4 (Box 1542)
    - Note: [letter from Douglas Aircraft Company Public Relations to Lowell Thomas concerning photographs taken during television shooting], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking to a crowd], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas being filmed as he delivers a speech], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas giving a speech underneath an airplane], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas delivering a speech underneath an airplane], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking in front of a group of people], 6
    - [An audience listenes to Lowell Thomas speak], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with an unidentified man], 8
  - Subject files: Theodora Duncan [color photograph], 1968; 5 (Box 1542)
    - To Mr. Lowell Thomas- to commemorate your visit to Hollywood on Jan. 2, 1968 Theodora Duncan, 1
    - Verso: To Mr. Lowell Thomas- to commemorate your visit to Hollywood on Jan. 2, 1968 Theodora Duncan, 1-verso
  - Subject files: Dutch Treat Club, circa late 1960s; 6 (Box 1542)
    - [Vice President Spiro Agnew at microphone, Lowell Thomas seated at left], 1
    - [Vice President Spiro Agnew at microphone, Lowell Thomas seated at left], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas at microphone, Vice President Spiro Agnew seated at left], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and Vice President Spiro Agnew seated at center], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking to a group of men at the Dutch Treat Club], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with an unidentified man at the Dutch Treat Club], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas with two men at the Dutch Treat Club], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with two unidentified men], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas and an unidentified man holding a painting], 9
  - Subject files: Norman Dyhrenfurth, circa 1960s; 7 (Box 1542)
    - [Lowell Thomas with Norman Dyhrenfurth], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas, a woman, and Norman Dyrenfurth], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with Norman Dyrenfurth], 3
  - Subject files: Early Atlantic fliers (Charles Lindbergh, Clarence D. Chamberlin, Amelia Earhart and others), circa 1930s; 8 (Box 1542)
    - In pix: Amelia Earhart [seated second from left], Chas. Lindbergh [standing second from left], etc. [Clarence D. Chamberlin? seated at left, Bernt Balchen standing at right, Lowell Thomas seated at right], 1
    - Verso: In pix: Amelia Earhart [seated second from left], Chas. Lindbergh [standing second from left], etc. [Clarence D. Chamberlin? seated at left, Bernt Balchen standing at right, Lowell Thomas seated at right], 1-verso
    - [Early Atlantic fliers: Amelia Earhart, Chas. Lindberg, Clarence D. Chamberlain, Bernt Balchen, Lowell Thomas]], 2
  - Subject files: Clyde Eddy (University of Denver), circa 1913; 9 (Box 1542)
    - Gamma Phi Beta sorority lodge at D. U. which will be completed and ready for occupancy the first of April, 1
    - Verso: Gamma Phi Beta sorority lodge at D. U. which will be completed and ready for occupancy the first of April, 1-verso
    - [Man (Clyde Eddy ?) and woman outside of a house], 2
  - Subject files: Clyde Eddy, 1941; 10 (Box 1542)
    - Clyde Eddy b. Mar. 30 1889; Clyde Eddy 1941, 1
    - Verso: Clyde Eddy b. Mar. 30 1889; Clyde Eddy 1941, 1-verso
  - Subject files: Dan Edwards, undated; 11 (Box 1542)
    - Note: Dan Edwards - Congressional Medal of Honor holder - World War I, 1
    - Dan Edwards - Congressional Medal of Honor holder - World War I, 2
    - Dan Edwards - Congressional Medal of Honor holder - World War I, 3
  - Subject files: European Skyways, 1926; 12 (Box 1542)
    - Note: Mr. and Mrs. L.T. at Templehof in Berlin with Gustav Lindenthal, famous patriarch and builder of the Hellgate Bridge, and Otto Merkle [Merkel], founder of Lufthansa, 1
    - Berlin, Mr. and Mrs. L.T. and aged Gustav Lindenthal builder of most of the Hudson River Bridges. This taken when Mr. + Mrs. L.T. were on a 25,000 mile sflight to 28 foreign countries, 2
    - Verso: Berlin, Mr. and Mrs. L.T. and aged Gustav Lindenthal builder of most of the Hudson River Bridges. This taken when Mr. + Mrs. L.T. were on a 25,000 mile sflight to 28 foreign countries, 2-verso
    - Berlin, Mr. and Mrs. L.T. and aged Gustav Lindenthal builder of most of the Hudson River Bridges. This taken when Mr. + Mrs. L.T. were on a 25,000 mile sflight to 28 foreign countries, 3
    - Berlin, Mr. and Mrs. L.T. and aged Gustav Lindenthal builder of most of the Hudson River Bridges. This taken when Mr. + Mrs. L.T. were on a 25,000 mile sflight to 28 foreign countries, 4
    - [Gustav Lindenthal, center, Otto Merkel, right], 5
    - In Munich, April 24th [Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas], 6
    - Verso: In Munich, April 24th [Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas], 6-verso
    - [Three men standing outside of a plane], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas in Munich], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas in Munich], 9
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing outside of an airplane in Munich], [2 copies], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas in Munich with a group of people], 11
  - Subject files: European Skyways, 1926; 13 (Box 1542)
    - Note: ripped note concerning European Skyways, 1
    - Note: Summary outline of European Skyways by Lowell Thomas in three pages [PDF file], 2
    - [European Skyways H-NACK plane], 3
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a city], 4
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a castle], 5
    - [European Skyways plane RR2 and D552], 6
    - [European Skyways RR2 plane flying over a city], 7
    - [European Skyways RR2 plane flying over a city street], 8
    - [European Skyways plane, RR2, flying over a large city], 9
    - [European Skyways plane, RR2, flying over a city], 10
    - [European Skyways plane RR2 ascending into the sky], 11
    - [European Skyways plane, K-SALO, flying over a European city], 12
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a European city], 13
    - [European Skyways bi-plane flying over Europe], 14
    - [European Skyways bi-plane flying over a European city], 15
    - [European Skyways bi-plane flying over a European city], 16
    - [Europeans Skyways plane over a city in Europe], 17
    - [European Skyways plane over an estate in Europe], 18
    - [European Skyways plane flying high above Europe], 19
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a canal in Europe], 20
    - [European Skyways plane flying over plateaus in Europe], 21
    - [European Skyways plane flying next to a cliff, over the sea], 22
    - [Praha, Czech Republic], 23
  - Subject files: European Skyways, 1926; 14 (Box 1542)
    - Prague, 1
    - Verso: Prague, 1-verso
    - Germany; Nachahmung wird strafrechtlich verfolgt. Alleiniges Urheberrecht bei Luftverkehr Strahle, Schorndorf (Wuttbg.), 2
    - Verso: Germany; Nachahmung wird strafrechtlich verfolgt. Alleiniges Urheberrecht bei Luftverkehr Strahle, Schorndorf (Wurtt,), 2-verso
    - Germany; Nachahmung wird strafrechtlich verfolgt. Alleiniges Urheberrecht bei Luftverkehr Strahle, Schorndorf (Wurtt,), 3